Hello everyone and welcome back to EnglishPod.
大家好，欢迎回到EnglishPod。
My name is Marco.
我是Marco。
And my name is Catherine and today we have a very scary story.
我是Catherine，今天我们带来一个非常恐怖的故事。
Spooky.
阴森森的。
We're actually bringing you the first of our advanced media lessons and what better way
我们实际上要推出第一个高级媒体课程，还有什么比
to start it with than a scary story for Halloween.
用一个万圣节的恐怖故事来开始更好呢？
Than with.
比用。
So what better way to start this advanced media lesson than with a scary story.
所以，还有什么比用一个恐怖故事来开始这个高级媒体课程更好呢？
Right.
没错。
So Halloween is coming up and advanced media usually features a new story or some kind
万圣节快到了，高级媒体通常会有新故事或某种
of story that we can then kind of break down and talk about.
故事，然后我们可以分解并讨论它。
Just have a conversation about because you're advanced level learners and you want to have
只是聊一聊，因为你们是高级学习者，想要
fun with English.
用英语玩得开心。
So where is today's spooky story set Marco?
那么，今天这个阴森的故事发生在哪里，Marco？
Well it starts out with a guy who remembers something very scary that happened to him
嗯，故事从一个男人回忆起他小时候发生的一件非常可怕的事情开始。
when he was a kid.
好的，今天故事的主角之一是他的姑姥姥。
Okay and so one of the main characters in today's story is his great aunt.
没错，他的姑姥姥。
That's right his great aunt.
所以基本上，这是一个家庭成员，但它是你父亲的姑姑。
And so basically this is a family member but it's your father's aunt.
对。
Right.
你的祖母或祖父的姐妹。
Your grandmother or your grandfather's sister.
对。
Right.
好吧，所以你的姑姑或姨妈是你父母的兄弟姐妹。
Alright so your aunt or your aunt is your parent's sibling.
但在这个情况下，我们说的是比那大一辈的人。
But in this case we're talking about one generation older than that.
所以你可以说姑姥姥、姑姥爷、曾祖父、曾祖母。
So you could say great aunt, great uncle, great grandfather, great grandmother.
就像往后退一步。
It's like one step back.
所以这通常是一个非常老的人，而姑姥姥绝对是今天故事中
So this is usually a very old person and the great aunt is definitely an important character
一个重要角色。
in today's story.
没错。
Exactly.
那我们就不让你再悬念了。
So let's not keep you in suspense any longer.
我们为什么不听听这个恐怖故事，然后回来讨论它。
Why don't we listen to this scary story and we'll be right back to talk about it.
哦不，灯灭了。
Oh no the lights went out.
亲爱的，你能点根蜡烛吗？
Honey can you light a candle?
当然。
Sure.
我们现在怎么办？
What do we do now?
嗯，我们可以像以前一样聊聊天。
Well we can just talk you know like we used to.
我知道。
I know.
我给你讲个恐怖故事。
I'll tell you a scary story.
它发生在我和我爸爸身上，那时我十几岁。
It happened to me and my dad when I was a teenager.
I was living with my father at the time when he received a phone call.
当时我和父亲住在一起，他接到了一个电话。
Hello.
你好。
Yes this is him.
是的，我就是。
I see.
我明白了。
Sorry to hear that.
听到这个消息很难过。
Okay no problem.
好的，没问题。
I'll be there shortly.
我马上就到。
Pack some clothes Tony.
收拾几件衣服，托尼。
My great aunt is very ill and no one in the family wants to take care of her.
我的姑姥姥病得很重，家里没人愿意照顾她。
We're going to stay at her house for a few days.
我们要去她家住几天。
Aunt?
姑姥姥？
What aunt?
什么姑姥姥？
I never knew you had a great aunt.
我从不知道你还有个姑姥姥。
Well the family doesn't talk about her or get near her for that matter.
嗯，家里人不谈论她，也不靠近她。
Why is that?
为什么？
Come on we have to go.
快，我们得走了。
So we arrived at this old house on the outskirts of our town.
于是我们来到了镇郊的一栋老房子。
There was almost no one around and the house had an eerie look to it.
周围几乎没人，房子看起来阴森森的。
Once inside the house we walked to her room and I was surprised to find my dad's great
一进房子，我们走到她的房间，我惊讶地发现父亲的姑姥姥坐在轮椅上，
aunt in a wheelchair yelling at someone but we were alone in the room.
对着什么人喊叫，但房间里只有我们。
Hi Aunt Ursula.
你好，乌苏拉姑姥姥。
This is my son Tony.
这是我儿子托尼。
Why have you come?
你们为什么来？
Why are you here?
你们为什么在这儿？
Don't you know it isn't safe?
难道不知道这里不安全吗？
My time is near.
我的时间快到了。
He's coming for me.
他要来找我了。
Who is coming for you?
谁要来找你？
The Prince of Darkness.
黑暗王子。
The Lord of the Underworld.
冥界之主。
The Tempter.
诱惑者。
The Old Serpent.
古蛇。
Come on.
来吧。
Aunt Ursula let's lay you down.
乌苏拉姑姥姥，我们扶你躺下。
You need to get some rest.
你需要休息一下。
Tony help me lay her down.
托尼，帮我扶她躺下。
That night we slept in one of the 12 rooms of that big old mansion.
那晚，我们睡在那栋大宅的十二个房间之一。
The trees outside seemed to come alive and their shadows formed ghoulish shapes on my
外面的树仿佛活了过来，它们的影子在我床上投下鬼魅般的形状。
bed.
床。
All of a sudden we heard screaming.
突然，我们听到了尖叫声。
Oh my God!
哦，我的天哪！
I can't believe it!
我简直不敢相信！
I won't let you take me!
我不会让你带走我的！
Oh my God!
哦，我的天哪！
I can't believe it!
我简直不敢相信！
I won't let you take me!
我不会让你带走我的！
Oh my God!
哦，我的天哪！
I can't believe it!
我简直不敢相信！
I won't let you take me!
我不会让你带走我的！
Oh my God!
哦，我的天哪！
I can't believe it!
我简直不敢相信！
I won't let you take me!
我不会让你带走我的！
Dad!
爸爸！
Something is attacking Aunt Ursula.
有东西在攻击厄休拉姑妈。
The door is jammed, stand back!
门卡住了，往后退！
Aunt Ursula where are you?
厄休拉姑妈，你在哪儿？
Over here!
在这儿！
And as we approached her she was lying on the floor with her hands and feet open like
当我们走近她时，她躺在地上，手脚张开，像
the Vitruvian Man, breathing heavily with bloody marks and scratches on her arms, legs
维特鲁威人一样，呼吸沉重，手臂、腿和脸上有血痕和抓伤。
and face.
和脸上。
Remember how I mentioned that she was in a wheelchair?
还记得我提过她坐轮椅吗？
My aunt had been paralyzed from the neck down for just over a year.
我姑妈从脖子以下瘫痪已经一年多了。
After this incident, strange things would happen in the house and my aunt would yell
这件事之后，房子里开始发生奇怪的事情，我姑妈会大喊
and scream, according to her, warding off the evil that had come to get her.
尖叫，据她说，是为了驱赶来找她的邪恶。
As the days passed, she became very weak and eventually was unable to talk.
日子一天天过去，她变得非常虚弱，最后连话都说不出来了。
My dad had to work during the day, so I was left to care for her.
我爸爸白天要上班，所以由我来照顾她。
When she lost her voice and laid on her deathbed, I would hear her breathe in and out.
当她失声躺在临终床上时，我能听到她呼吸的声音。
Until finally one day, she breathed in and never exhaled.
直到有一天，她吸了一口气，再也没有呼出来。
That night, I felt relieved that it was finally over, but it wasn't.
那天晚上，我感到如释重负，以为终于结束了，但事实并非如此。
I was so terrified of what I was hearing that I didn't sleep all night.
我被听到的声音吓坏了，整晚都没睡。
The following morning, I went to the bathroom, expecting to find a mess and everything torn
第二天早上，我去洗手间，以为会看到一片狼藉，东西都被撕碎了，
up, but I found everything exactly as it was before.
但我发现一切都和以前一模一样。
The movers came that same day and as we were cleaning out her drawers and personal items,
搬家工人当天就来了，当我们清理她的抽屉和私人物品时，
we found strange notebooks with names and amounts of money written next to them.
我们发现了奇怪的笔记本，上面写着名字和旁边的金额。
We found pictures with people's faces sewn with black or red string.
我们发现了照片，上面的人脸用黑色或红色的线缝着。
And you want to know what the strangest thing was?
你想知道最奇怪的是什么吗？
There was a small doll filled with dead ants, with a strand of hair tied around its waist.
有一个小娃娃，里面装满了死蚂蚁，腰上缠着一缕头发。
And on the doll's face, there was a picture of me with the numbers 31-10-09.
而在娃娃的脸上，有一张我的照片，上面写着数字31-10-09。
You know what date it is today?
你知道今天是什么日期吗？
October 31st, 2009.
2009年10月31日。
Alright, we're back.
好了，我们回来了。
So, what did you think?
那么，你觉得怎么样？
Pretty scary?
挺吓人的吧？
I got goosebumps.
我起了一身鸡皮疙瘩。
It's a little spooky.
有点瘆人。
A little scary.
有点吓人。
Now, what's interesting about this story, it's based on a true story, so that makes
现在，这个故事有趣的地方在于，它是根据真实事件改编的，所以这让它
it even scarier.
更吓人了。
No.
不会吧。
Yeah.
真的。
Dare I ask, did this happen to you?
我敢问一句，这事发生在你身上吗？
No, no.
不，不。
I'm not old enough, but this actually happened to a family member of mine, and that's why
我还没那么老，但这确实发生在我一个亲戚身上，这就是为什么
I know this story.
我知道这个故事。
So, it was kind of told to me when I was a bit younger and I remembered it.
所以，这是我小时候听别人讲的，我一直记得。
And well, Halloween is a great time to remember these things.
嗯，万圣节正是回忆这些事情的好时候。
And the first time you heard it, it scared the crap out of you, right?
你第一次听到的时候，肯定吓得屁滚尿流，对吧？
Oh yeah, for sure.
哦，那当然。
Actually, the first time I heard it, we were on an airplane, like on October 31st.
实际上，我第一次听到它时，我们正在飞机上，正好是10月31日。
Oh wow.
哦，哇。
So, it was pretty scary.
所以，那挺吓人的。
Well, we've got a lot of really interesting stuff here.
好了，我们这里有很多非常有趣的内容。
We're not going to dwell too long on the grammar or the vocabulary because we assume that most
我们不会在语法或词汇上花太多时间，因为我们假设大多数
of you have understood this, but there are a couple of things that can be really difficult
人都已经理解了，但有几件事即使对英语母语者来说
even for English speakers.
也可能很难。
So, the first one is this phrase, my time is near.
所以，第一个是这个短语，“我的时辰近了”。
My time is near.
我的时辰近了。
So, what does that mean exactly?
那么，这到底是什么意思呢？
Well, my time is near, my end is coming.
嗯，“我的时辰近了”，就是我的末日要来了。
It means I'm very old and I'm probably going to die soon.
意思是我很老了，可能很快就要死了。
So my time, his time, that's when you die.
所以“我的时辰”、“他的时辰”，就是指你死的时候。
Okay, so it's always used in reference to death, right?
好的，所以它总是和死亡有关，对吧？
In this case, yeah.
在这个故事里，是的。
So, it's used in reference to death and in this case, we have the aunt who's talking
所以，它用来指代死亡，在这个故事里，是那位姑婆在谈论
about herself, but you could also say his time is coming, we should visit him in the
她自己，但你也可以说“他的时辰要到了，我们应该去医院看看他”。
hospital.
So, it's a kind of softer way of saying that someone is going to die soon.
所以，这是一种比较委婉的说法，表示某人快要死了。
Right.
对。
Okay, so my time is near or his time is near.
好的，所以“我的时辰近了”或“他的时辰近了”。
All right.
好的。
And then, something really interesting in this story as well, she had many different
然后，这个故事里还有一个非常有趣的地方，她用了很多不同的
names that she called the devil.
名字来称呼魔鬼。
So, she didn't directly say the devil, she said the prince of darkness.
所以，她没有直接说“魔鬼”，而是说了“黑暗王子”。
Prince of darkness, lord of the underworld, the tempter.
“黑暗王子”、“冥界之主”、“诱惑者”。
The tempter and the old serpent.
“诱惑者”和“古蛇”。
So, these are actually different ways that historically have been used to describe the
这些其实都是历史上用来描述
devil, right?
魔鬼的不同方式，对吧？
That's right.
没错。
And a lot of them are biblical, like the old serpent, you know, back in the first pages
其中很多都来自圣经，比如“古蛇”，你知道，在圣经的开头几页
of the Bible when the serpent tempts Eve, that's the devil.
里，蛇引诱夏娃的时候，那就是魔鬼。
And so, we hear a lot of these, especially on Halloween, these are great words to use
所以，我们经常听到这些，尤其是在万圣节，这些词很适合用来
to kind of diversify and not say devil, devil, devil.
丰富表达，而不是一直说“魔鬼、魔鬼、魔鬼”。
Right.
对。
Okay.
好的。
So, apart from those synonyms for the devil, she also used an interesting phrase towards
那么，除了这些魔鬼的同义词，她在结尾处还用了一个有趣的短语，
the end when she said, I shall be judged before you can take me.
她说：“在你抓到我之前，我必先受审判。”
Hmm.
嗯。
So, judged, to judge, this is to see if something is right or wrong.
所以，“judged”（受审判），“to judge”（审判），就是判断某事是对是错。
But in this case, we talk about judgment at the end of a person's life.
但在这里，我们谈论的是一个人生命终结时的审判。
So, that means when you go to the gates of heaven and there's Saint Peter and he has
也就是说，当你走到天堂门口，圣彼得在那里，他拿着
a list of the good and the bad and he says yes or no.
一份善恶清单，然后他说“行”或“不行”。
Right.
对。
And then if you're a no, you get sent down to hell.
然后如果你被说“不行”，你就会被送到地狱。
If you're a yes, you go to heaven.
如果你被说“行”，你就去天堂。
So, she says, I shall be judged.
所以，她说：“我必先受审判。”
This means, I want my day in court.
这意味着，我想要我的“法庭日”。
I want to have my actions analyzed by Saint Peter, not by you.
我想让圣彼得来评判我的行为，而不是你。
Right, exactly.
对，完全正确。
So, actually, this makes reference to a lot of beliefs in Christianity, right?
所以，实际上，这引用了很多基督教的信仰，对吧？
So, it's just another aspect of the story.
所以，这只是故事的另一个方面。
But of course, other religions probably don't have the same things such as the gates of
但当然，其他宗教可能没有像天堂之门
heaven and Saint Peter.
和圣彼得这样的东西。
Right, the system of judgment.
对，审判体系。
Alright.
好的。
So, what did you think of the story?
那么，你觉得这个故事怎么样？
Did you like it?
你喜欢吗？
I really liked it.
我真的很喜欢。
I thought it was really spooky and I thought that it built up well.
我觉得它非常瘆人，而且铺垫得很好。
But I really also like the imagery.
但我也很喜欢其中的意象。
We talked about, or we haven't talked about this yet, but he describes his great aunt,
我们谈到了，或者说我们还没谈到这个，但他描述他的姑婆，
the character describes his great aunt as being spread out like the Vitruvian man.
角色描述他的姑婆像“维特鲁威人”一样伸展着。
So, you have this image of her arms spread out and her legs spread out.
所以，你脑海中浮现出她双臂张开、双腿张开的画面。
You know that picture that da Vinci did of a human being and it's like an anatomy and
你知道达芬奇画的那幅人体画，像解剖图一样，
it's in a circle and you can see the legs and the arms.
在一个圆圈里，你能看到腿和胳膊。
That's just so really like a powerful visual image.
那真是一个非常有力的视觉形象。
Yeah, you can imagine her laying on the bed in this position, right?
是啊，你可以想象她以这个姿势躺在床上，对吧？
Yeah, it is pretty scary.
嗯，确实挺吓人的。
What about you?
你呢？
Have you ever had any close encounters with the supernatural or ghosts or goblins or something
你有没有过与超自然现象、鬼魂、小妖精之类的
like this?
近距离接触的经历？
No, personally I've never had any experiences like that and I tend to not believe those
没有，我个人从来没有过这样的经历，而且我倾向于不相信那些
stories but maybe if this had happened to someone I knew I'd be a little bit more skeptical
故事，但如果这发生在我认识的人身上，我可能会更怀疑一点，
or less skeptical.
或者说没那么怀疑。
What about when they have those documentaries or those recordings of strange voices or
那那些纪录片，或者那些奇怪声音或影像的录音呢，
appearances like these old castles in England or stuff like that?
比如英国那些古老城堡之类的？
What do you think?
你怎么看？
I love those shows.
我喜欢那些节目。
I just watched one and it was about a haunted house.
我刚看了一个，是关于一个鬼屋的。
There was a woman who used a Ouija board and it let a demon out and the demon possessed
有一个女人用了通灵板，结果放出了一个恶魔，恶魔附身
the girl and they called in a priest and the priest had to like exorcise the demon from
在一个女孩身上，他们叫来了一个神父，神父不得不给
the little girl and the house was haunted and it was hurting people and it was like
小女孩驱魔，房子闹鬼，它伤害人，还
possessing people.
附身于人。
Wow, it sounds like a movie.
哇，听起来像电影一样。
Yeah, it does but it was like a TV show on Discovery Channel and it was really, really
是啊，确实像，但那是探索频道的一个电视节目，真的非常非常
fun.
有趣。
I don't actually believe that a spirit could push someone down the stairs.
我其实不相信一个幽灵能把人推下楼梯。
I think that you trip and then you attribute it to a spirit.
我觉得是你自己绊倒了，然后把它归咎于幽灵。
What about the Ouija board?
那通灵板呢？
That's an interesting tool that many people say opens up portals and dimensions towards
那是一个有趣的工具，很多人说它能打开通往地狱的
hell or spirits can come out and stuff like that.
门户或维度，让幽灵出来之类的。
Well, for those of you who don't know, the Ouija board is a board, like a piece of cardboard
嗯，对于那些不知道的人来说，通灵板是一块板子，像一块硬纸板，
that has letters on it, letters and numbers.
上面有字母，字母和数字。
You have this glass that you hold and once the spirit comes, it guides the glass to point
你拿着一个玻璃杯，一旦幽灵来了，它会引导玻璃杯指向
out to names or places and you spell them.
名字或地点，然后你拼出来。
They're really popular with like 13-year-old girls who have these slumber parties and they
它们在13岁左右的小女孩中很流行，她们开睡衣派对时
use it and we always say, you know, who is she going to date and then it moves.
会用它，我们总是问，你知道，她会和谁约会，然后它就会动。
But yeah, I believe in the power of the human mind so I think a lot of times even if we're
但没错，我相信人类心智的力量，所以我认为很多时候，即使我们
not aware of it, we're the ones manipulating this.
我们并没有意识到，其实是我们自己在操控这一切。
Or believing what we want to believe.
或者只相信我们想相信的东西。
Yeah, but what about you?
是啊，那你呢？
Are you superstitious?
你迷信吗？
Do you believe in ghosts?
你相信有鬼吗？
I'm not superstitious.
我不迷信。
I don't know what to think about ghosts because I've actually had a couple of very strange
我不知道该怎么看待鬼魂，因为我确实有过几次非常奇怪的
encounters with the supernatural but I really wouldn't say, oh yeah, I believe in ghosts
超自然遭遇，但我真的不会说，哦，是的，我相信有鬼，
or I believe there are spirits that haven't been put to rest or they have unfinished business,
或者我相信有未安息的灵魂，或者它们有未了的心愿，
you know, like in Casper or something like that.
你知道，就像《鬼马小精灵》里那样。
But once we were having dinner with my family in the house where we used to live and it
但有一次，我和家人在我们以前住的房子里吃晚饭，那
was a very old house and we had a glass of water on the table and all of a sudden it
是一栋很老的房子，桌上放着一杯水，突然它
started to move and to rotate across the table, the center of the table and we all saw it
开始移动，在桌子上旋转，穿过桌子中央，我们都看到了，
and no one was touching it.
而且没人碰它。
So we all were pretty confused and nervous and then just kind of burst out in nervous
所以我们都很困惑和紧张，然后突然紧张地
laughter and we didn't really know what to make of it but it was very strange because
大笑起来，我们真的不知道该怎么解释，但这事非常奇怪，因为
it moved a good amount, it was like half of the table and it was spinning at the same
它移动了很大一段距离，大概有半张桌子，同时还在旋转，
time so it was very strange.
所以非常奇怪。
Weird.
真诡异。
So, things like this and, you know, in general Hispanic or Latin American culture are, they're
所以，像这样的事情，而且你知道，总的来说，西班牙裔或拉丁美洲文化，它们
very superstitious.
非常迷信。
They have a lot of beliefs in like magic or some people still say, are reluctant to give
他们有很多关于魔法之类的信仰，有些人仍然说，不愿意
out a picture for example because of something like this in the story.
给别人照片，比如因为类似故事里的这种事。
Really?
真的吗？
They don't give out pictures to boyfriends or girlfriends or anyone because if you break
他们不给男朋友、女朋友或任何人照片，因为如果你们
up or something is to happen then they could do something with that picture and maybe hurt
分手或发生什么事，他们可以用那张照片做点什么，可能会伤害
you.
你。
Really?
真的吗？
So this idea that you have a likeness, like a picture or a doll or something, can you
所以这种想法，就是你有肖像，比如照片、玩偶之类的东西，你能
talk about that because I don't really know anything about it.
谈谈这个吗？因为我对此真的不太了解。
Having that means that you're able to like do something to that very person?
拥有那个东西就意味着你能对那个人做些什么吗？
Yeah, yeah.
是的，是的。
Like, not necessarily like a voodoo doll, right?
比如，不一定像巫毒娃娃那样，对吧？
Where you see that you can put pins in it and then it would hurt someone.
就是你可以在上面插针，然后就会伤害到某人。
But people believe that pictures, for example, they capture your image and so if somebody
但人们相信，比如照片，它们捕捉了你的形象，所以如果有人
has it and wants to do harm or black magic then they can use that as an instrument to
拥有它，并且想伤害你或施黑魔法，他们就可以用它作为工具
get into you.
来影响你。
Okay.
好吧。
The same as pieces of clothing or the same as hair and things like this.
同样，还有衣服、头发之类的东西。
So that's why there are the shamans or the Indian witch doctors who do cleansing like
所以这就是为什么有萨满或印第安巫医做这样的净化仪式，
this and people still actually go to them.
人们实际上仍然会去找他们。
People in the city still believe in these things and they'll go to a shaman and get
城里的人仍然相信这些东西，他们会去找萨满，让
themselves cleansed because they believe that their luck, they have really bad luck or they've
自己得到净化，因为他们相信自己的运气，他们运气非常差，或者他们
been very, very sick for a long time and doctors can't figure out what it is.
病了很久，医生也查不出是什么问题。
They think it's because someone has cast a spell on them or is doing some black magic
他们认为是因为有人对他们施了咒，或者对他们施了黑魔法，
to them and they need to get it cleansed.
他们需要净化。
Oh, wow.
哦，哇。
So, yeah, it's really, really common.
所以，是的，这真的很常见。
But it's all part of the folklore and the heritage of the countries.
但这都是这些国家民间传说和文化遗产的一部分。
It's actually very, very interesting and some things are just really out there, really weird.
实际上非常非常有趣，有些东西真的很离谱，很奇怪。
Yeah?
是吗？
Yeah.
是的。
Well, a lot of it I think comes from indigenous beliefs mixing with Catholicism too, right?
嗯，我觉得很多都来自土著信仰与天主教的融合，对吧？
Yeah, exactly.
是的，没错。
Because a lot of South American countries and Latin American countries are very Catholic
因为很多南美国家和拉丁美洲国家都非常信奉天主教，
but they get kind of melded, these traditions with indigenous beliefs and then you have
但这些传统与土著信仰融合在一起，然后就有了
these crazy rituals and like...
这些疯狂的仪式，比如……
We actually have a belief and it's very true that when somebody is completely in love with
我们实际上有一种信仰，而且很真实，就是当一个人完全爱上
this girl and this girl is maybe not very nice or not very nice to that guy but he's
这个女孩，而这个女孩可能对他不太好，但他
still completely into her.
仍然完全迷恋她。
So, there's this word that we say that he's been like underweared or something like that.
所以，我们有一个词来形容他，说他被“内裤”了之类的。
And the reason behind this is that one of these rituals that I talked about is that
这背后的原因是，我提到的其中一个仪式是，
the girl would make tea, right?
女孩会泡茶，对吧？
Would take a tea pot and in it would put her underpants, used underpants to make the tea
她会拿一个茶壶，在里面放她的内裤，用过的内裤来泡茶
water and then would serve it to the guy.
水，然后端给那个男人喝。
So, the moment that he drank it, this was like a magic potion and then he would continuously
所以，他一喝下去，这就像一种魔法药水，然后他就会一直
be in love with her.
爱着她。
Oh.
哦。
So, yeah, it's very strange.
所以，是的，这很奇怪。
That's gross.
真恶心。
Do people actually do that?
人们真的会这么做吗？
No.
不。
It's not something that you do now but it's something that people knew about that used
这不是你现在会做的事，但这是人们知道的，以前
to be done way, way before.
很久以前有人做过的事。
Okay.
好吧。
So, people now...
所以，现在的人……
It's part of the language where you say that someone has been like...
这是语言的一部分，你会说某人被……
Underweared or something like that.
“内裤”了之类的。
She cast a spell on him maybe what we would say.
她对他施了咒，也许我们会这么说。
So, things like this that of course aren't really done anymore but still people make
所以，像这样的事情，当然现在不再真的做了，但人们仍然
reference to it because we know it from our history that it's been done before.
会提到它，因为我们从历史中知道它曾经发生过。
How cool.
真酷。
Well, I'm really curious to know if our users have any similar stories or have any scary
嗯，我很好奇我们的用户有没有类似的故事，或者有没有什么吓人的
stories they want to tell.
故事想讲。
I bet they do.
我打赌他们有。
I'm sure they do.
我肯定他们有。
And this advanced media lesson is a great place for you to do that because we expect
而这个高级媒体课程是一个很好的地方让你这么做，因为我们预计
that a lot of advanced level learners are going to be listening to it and practicing
会有很多高级水平的学习者会听它，练习
your writing is really important.
写作真的很重要。
So, we hope that you'll put some comments on this lesson and of course ask us as many
所以，我们希望你能在这节课上留下一些评论，当然，也尽可能多地
questions as you want.
问我们问题。
All right.
好的。
So, we'll see you guys there and have a happy Halloween.
那么，我们就在那里见你们了，祝万圣节快乐。
Happy Halloween.
万圣节快乐。
Bye.
再见。